<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="title_activity_manual">Manual</string>

    <string name="manual_games">Games</string>
    <string name="manual_feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="manual_startpage">Start page</string>
    <string name="manual_back_to_game">Back to game</string>
    <string name="manual_structure">Structure</string>
    <string name="manual_objective">Objective</string>
    <string name="manual_rules">Rules</string>
    <string name="manual_scoring">Scoring</string>
    <string name="manual_main_menu">Main menu</string>
    <string name="manual_ui">User interface</string>
    <string name="page_load_error">No page for this game available…</string>
    <string name="manual_bonus">After winning a game, you get a bonus: The faster you win, the higher the bonus will be.</string>


    <!-- Feedback -->
    <string name="manual_open_google_play">Open Google Play</string>
    <string name="manual_open_github">Open GitHub Repo</string>
    <!-- Games -->
    <string name="manual_games_text1">Choose a game to show it\'s structure, objective, rules and scoring.</string>
    <string name="manual_startpage_text">Welcome to the manual of this game collection! I hope it will explain everything.
        \n\nUse the menu on the left side to access the other manual pages.</string>
    <string name="manual_general_main_menu">The usage of the main menu is relatively simple. Just tap on a game to start it.
        \n\nThe app will automatically load the last played game on a restart, if the app was paused in it. This behavior can
        be disabled in the settings under \"General\".\n\nThere you can also find the section \"Main menu\", where it\'s possible to hide games
        from the menu and change the number of columns, so more games fit on the screen at once.</string>
    <string name="manual_ui_text">A game will always show a little menu on the bottom part of the screen (Portrait mode) or on the
        right side (Landscape mode). It will also show the current score and current played time of the game. If possible, these two values
        will be saved for the high-score list. The menu contains 5 items, which have the following effects (buttons
        from left to right):\n\nThe \"Scores\" button will show a new window with the high scores and the count of won games of
        the current game.\n\nThe \"Hint\" button will help you by showing up to 3 possible card movements at once. But this will decrease
        the current score by 25. Notice that trivial movements like moving every card to an empty field or pressing on the main
        stack aren\'t shown as a hint. If no hint was shown, the score won\'t decrease.\n\nThe \"Menu\" button shows three different
        actions: Start a new game by mixing the cards and drawing a new deal. Give cards again will do the same but without the
        mixing. So it\'s like a restart of the current game. The last option will end the current game and return the app to the
        main menu.\n\nThe \"Undo\" button will revert the last movement, but this will cost 25 points. This can be used for up to
        20 last movements.\n\nThe \"Settings\" button simply opens the settings menu.</string>
    <string name="manual_feedback_text">Found a bug or an error? Something I should improve? Should I add another game to the
        collection? Maybe you want to help with some translations? Or have another idea?\n\nI am happy to receive any kind of
        feedback. If you feel the need to contact me, you should consider the following two options:\n\nUse the Issue Tracker
        on GitHub: The project of this app on GitHub has a neat function to report issues. Just click on the button on the left
        side of the screen to open the Issue Tracker with the Internet browser.\n\nUse a rating in Google Play: Just leave a
        rating on the page from this app and write anything you want in it. Click on the button to the right side to open the
        Google Play Store (if installed).\n\nThank you in advance for your feedback :)</string>

    <!-- Klondike -->
    <string name="manual_Klondike_structure">1 deck of 52 cards.\n\n7 tableau stacks, 4 foundation
        stacks, 1 main and 1 discard stack.</string>
    <string name="manual_Klondike_objective">Order every card in real families in ascending order on
        the foundation.</string>
    <string name="manual_Klondike_rules">Cards can be placed on the tableau in descending order and
        in alternating colors. You can move a whole sequence of cards at once. On the foundation, cards
        can be placed only in ascending order on the corresponding family.\n\nOnly kings can be placed
        on empty tableau stacks and only aces can be placed on empty foundation stacks.\n\nBy pressing
        on the main stack, cards will be moved to the discard stack from where you can use them.
        The amount of cards depends on the chosen settings. If \"Draw 1\" has been selected, only one card
        will be moved (This is the default setting, for easier game play). With \"Draw 3\" enabled, 3 cards
        will be moved at once.\n\nIf the main stack is empty, you can still press on it to move every
        card from the discard stack to the main stack and use them again.</string>
    <string name="manual_Klondike_scoring">From tableau to foundation: +60\n\nFrom discard stack to
        foundation: +45\n\nFrom foundation to tableau: -75\n\nTurn a card over: +25\n\nReturn all cards
        from discard stack to main stack: -200</string>

    <!-- FreeCell -->
    <string name="manual_Freecell_structure">1 deck of 52 cards.\n\n8 tableau stacks, 4 foundation
        stacks and 4 free cells.</string>
    <string name="manual_Freecell_objective">Order every card in real families in ascending order on
        the foundation.</string>
    <string name="manual_Freecell_rules">Cards can be placed on the tableau in descending order and
        in alternating colors. On the foundation, cards can be placed only in ascending order on the
        corresponding family. The 4 cells on the top can only contain one card at a time.\n\nYou can
        move as many cards (which are in a correct sequence) at once, as there are free stacks (tableau
        and the cells) available. This corresponds to the rule, that only one card can be moved at once,
        but when there are free stacks available, the cards can be moved on the free stacks first and then
        to the destination stack.\n\nEvery card can be placed on empty tableau fields and cells. Aces can
        be placed on empty foundation fields.</string>
    <string name="manual_Freecell_scoring">Move a card to foundation: +60\n\nMove a card from foundation:
        -75\n\nMove a king to an empty field: +20</string>

    <!-- Yukon -->
    <string name="manual_Yukon_structure">1 deck of 52 cards.\n\n7 tableau stacks and 4 foundation stacks.</string>
    <string name="manual_Yukon_objective">Order every card in real families in ascending order on the foundation.</string>
    <string name="manual_Yukon_rules">Cards can be placed on the tableau in descending order and in
        alternating colors. On the foundation, cards can be placed only in ascending order on the
        corresponding family.\n\nYou can move every faced up card, no matter how many cards and
        which sequence the cards are on top of it.\n\nOnly kings can be placed on empty tableau
        fields and only aces can be placed on empty foundation fields.</string>
    <string name="manual_Yukon_scoring">From tableau to foundation: +60\n\nFrom foundation to tableau:
        -75\n\nMove a king to an empty field: +20\n\nFlip a card up: +25</string>

    <!-- Spider -->
    <string name="manual_Spider_structure">2 decks of 52 cards.\n\n10 tableau stacks and 8 foundation
        stacks.\n\n1 main stack, separated in 5 different piles.\n\nDepending on settings: 1, 2 or 4
        different card families.</string>
    <string name="manual_Spider_objective">Place every card in true descending card families anywhere on the
        tableau. The built card families will be automatically moved to the foundation.</string>
    <string name="manual_Spider_rules">Cards can be placed on any card in descending order. But only
        real card family sequences can be moved at once.\n\nEvery card can be placed on empty tableau
        stacks.\n\nPress on the main stack to deal one card to every tableau stack at once.</string>
    <string name="manual_Spider_scoring">Move a card family to foundation: +200\n\n
        Flip a card up: +25</string>

    <!-- SimpleSimon -->
    <string name="manual_SimpleSimon_structure">1 deck of 52 cards.\n\n10 tableau stacks and 4
        foundation stacks.</string>
    <string name="manual_SimpleSimon_objective">Place every card in true descending card families anywhere
        on the tableau. The built card families will be automatically moved to the foundation.</string>
    <string name="manual_SimpleSimon_rules">Cards can be placed on any card in descending order.
        But only real card family sequences can be moved at once.\n\nEvery card can be placed on
        empty tableau stacks.</string>
    <string name="manual_SimpleSimon_scoring">Move a card family to foundation: +200</string>

    <!-- Golf -->
    <string name="manual_Golf_structure">1 deck of 52 cards.\n\n7 tableau stacks, 1 main and 1
        discard stack.\n\nMoving cards from the discard stack back to the main stack is not possible (Expect from using the Undo button).</string>
    <string name="manual_Golf_objective">Move every card from the tableau to the discard stack.</string>
    <string name="manual_Golf_rules">Every top card of a stack can be used to play. Cards can only be
        placed on the discard stack in ascending and descending order regardless of color.\n\nDepending
        on settings, you can also place a king on an ace and vice versa (easier game play).\n\nIf no
        card can be moved, press on the main stack to deal one card from it to the discard stack.</string>
    <string name="manual_Golf_scoring">Move a card to the discard stack: +50</string>

    <!-- Pyramid -->
    <string name="manual_Pyramid_structure">1 deck of 52 cards.\n\n28 tableau stacks, 1 main, 1 discard and 1
        waste stack.\n\nCards from the discard stack can be moved back to the main stack only two times in a game.</string>
    <string name="manual_Pyramid_objective">Move every card from the tableau to the waste. Depending
        on settings, also every card from
        main and discard stacks has to be moved to the waste.</string>
    <string name="manual_Pyramid_rules">This game has slightly different rules compared to the other Solitare games.
        Every card, which isn\'t covered by another card can be played. Two cards, whose values add up to 13 can be moved to the
        waste. To do so, move a card on another free card. If both values are correct, they will be
        automatically moved to the waste.\n\nIt is also possible to use the cards from main and discard stack.
        If no card movement is possible, press on the arrow between these stacks to
        move one card from the main stack to the discard stack. If the main stack is empty, press again on it or
        on the arrow to return the cards from the discard stack to the main stack. This movement can
        only be used two times in a game. The remaining amount will be shown as the little number above
        the arrow.</string>
    <string name="manual_Pyramid_scoring">Move a card to the waste: +50\n\nReturn all cards from
        discard stack to main stack: -200</string>

    <!-- TriPekas -->
    <string name="manual_TriPeaks_structure">1 deck of 52 cards.\n\n28 tableau stacks, 1 main and 1
        discard stack.\n\nMoving cards from the discard stack back to the main stack is not possible (Expect from using the Undo button).</string>
    <string name="manual_TriPeaks_objective">Move every card from the tableau to the discard stack.</string>
    <string name="manual_TriPeaks_rules">The rules of this game are similar to \"Golf\". Every card
        which isn\'t covered by another card can be used to play. Cards can only be placed on the
        discard stack in ascending and descending order regardless of color.\n\nIt is also possible
        to play kings on aces and vice versa.\n\nIf no card can be moved, press on the main stack to
        deal one card from it to the discard stack.</string>
    <string name="manual_TriPeaks_scoring">Move a card to the waste: +50</string>

    <!-- Forty&Eight -->
    <string name="manual_FortyEight_structure">2 deck of 52 cards.\n\n8 tableau stacks, 8 foundation
        stacks, 1 main and 1 discard stack.\n\nCards from the discard stack can be moved back to the
        main stack only once in a game.\n\n</string>
    <string name="manual_FortyEight_objective">Order every card as real families in ascending order
        on the foundation.</string>
    <string name="manual_FortyEight_rules">Cards can be placed on the tableau in descending order of
        the same family. On the foundation, cards can be placed only in ascending order on the corresponding family.

        \n\nYou can
        move as many cards (which are in a correct sequence) at once, as there are free stacks available.
        This corresponds to the rule, that only one card can be moved at once,
        but when there are free stacks available, the cards can be moved on the free stacks first and then
        to the destination stack.

        \n\nEvery card can be
        placed on empty tableau stacks and only aces can be placed on empty foundation stacks.\n\nBy
        pressing on the main stack, one card will be moved to the discard stack from where you can play
        it.\n\nIf the main stack is empty, you can still press on it to move every card from the
        discard stack back to the main stack and use them again. But this is only once a game possible.
        The remaining amount is shown a the little number above the main stack.</string>
    <string name="manual_FortyEight_scoring">Move a card to foundation: +45\n\nMove a card back to
        tableau: -60\n\nMove a card from the discard stack to tableau: +60\n\nReturn cards from discard to main stack: -200</string>

    <!-- Mod3 -->
    <string name="manual_mod3_structure">2 deck of 52 cards.\n\n32 tableau stacks, 1 main and 1 aces
        stack.</string>
    <string name="manual_mod3_objective">Order every card on the top 3 rows of the tableau as sequences
        of the same color in the following way:\n\nFirst row: Sequences of 2–5–8–J\nSecond row: Sequences
        of 3–6–9–Q\nThird row: Sequences of 4–7–10–K\n\nAces will be put away.</string>
    <string name="manual_mod3_rules">You can move only one card from the top of a stack at once. Cards can only
        be placed if the sequence shown under \"Objectives\" is correct. So you can place for example a
        Hearts 5 on a Hearts 2, but only if the Hearts 2 is in the first row of the tableau. Different
        families aren\'t allowed either.\n\nGain free stacks to place cards by moving aces to the aces
        stack above the main stack.\n\nThe fourth row is also the discard row for the cards from the main
        stack. Any card can be placed on a free stack of the forth row.\n\nPress on the main stack to deal
        one card to each stack of the forth row.</string>
    <string name="manual_mod3_scoring">Move a card on a correct field of the tableau: +50\n\nMove a card back to the fourth row of the tableau: -75</string>

    <!-- Gypsy -->
    <string name="manual_Gypsy_structure">2 deck of 52 cards.\n\n8 tableau stacks, 8 foundation stacks,
        and 1 main stack.</string>
    <string name="manual_Gypsy_objective">Order every card in real families in ascending order on the
        foundation.</string>
    <string name="manual_Gypsy_rules">Cards can be placed on the tableau in descending order and in
        alternating colors. You can move a whole correct sequence of cards at once. On the foundation,
        cards can be placed only in ascending order on the corresponding family.\n\nEvery card can be
        placed on empty tableau stacks and only aces can be placed on empty foundation stacks.\n\nBy
        pressing on the main stack, one card will be moved to each tableau stack.</string>
    <string name="manual_Gypsy_scoring">Move a card to foundation: +75\n\nMove a card from foundation to tableau: -100\n\n
        Flip a card over: +50</string>

    <!-- acesUp -->
    <string name="manual_AcesUp_structure">1 deck of 52 cards.\n\n4 tableau stacks, 1 main and 1
        foundation stack.\n\nAces have the value 14, so they have a higher value than kings.</string>
    <string name="manual_AcesUp_objective">Put all cards except the aces on the foundation stack,
        so there is one ace on every tableau stack left.</string>
    <string name="manual_AcesUp_rules">You can move only the top card of a stack. Move cards which
        have a lower value than another top card of the same family to the foundation. For example:
        There are a Hearts 5 and a Hearts 10 on top of two tableau stacks. Then you can move the Hearts
        5 to the foundation. Aces have a higher value than every other card.\n\nEvery movable card can
        be placed on empty tableau stacks.\n\nPress the main stack to deal one card to each tableau
        stack.</string>
    <string name="manual_AcesUp_scoring">Move a card to the foundation stack: +50</string>

    <!-- Canfield -->
    <string name="manual_Canfield_structure">1 deck of 52 cards.\n\n4 tableau stacks, 4 foundation
        stacks, 1 main, 1 discard stack and a reserve stack</string>
    <string name="manual_Canfield_objective">Order every card in real families in ascending order on
        the foundation.</string>
    <string name="manual_Canfield_rules">Cards can be placed on the tableau in descending order and
        in alternating colors. You can move a complete sequence of cards at once. On the foundation, cards
        can be placed only in ascending order on the corresponding family.\n\nEmpty
        tableau fields are filled with a card from the reserve. If the reserve is empty, a card from the main stack will be used.\n\nThe
        value of the first card drawn to the foundation will specify which cards can be placed on empty foundation fields.
        For example: If a Hearts 10 was drawn to the foundation, only cards with the value 10 can be placed on empty foundation fields.
        But the cards on the foundation can be placed cyclic, so it is also possible to play an ace on a king\n\nBy
        pressing on the main stack, cards will be moved to the discard stack from where you can use them.
        The amount of cards depends on the chosen settings. If \"Draw 1\" has been selected, only one card
        will be moved. With \"Draw 3\" enabled, 3 cards
        will be moved at once.\n\nIf the main stack is empty, you can still press on it to move every
        card from the discard stack to the main stack and use them again.</string>
    <string name="manual_Canfield_scoring">From tableau to foundation: +60\n\nFrom discard stack to
        foundation: +45\n\nFrom foundation to tableau: -75\n\nTurn a card over: +25\n\nReturn all cards
        from discard stack to main stack: -200</string>

    <!-- GrandfathersClock -->
    <string name="manual_GrandfathersClock_structure">1 deck of 52 cards.\n\n8 tableau stacks, 12 foundation
        stacks in the form of a clock. Each foundation stack already contains one card</string>
    <string name="manual_GrandfathersClock_objective">Order every card in real families in ascending order on
        the foundation. At the end, the card values on the foundation match the values on a clock.</string>
    <string name="manual_GrandfathersClock_rules">Cards can be placed on the tableau in descending order, the color doesn\'t matter.
        On the foundation, cards can be placed only in ascending order on the corresponding family. But Aces can be placed on top of kings.

        \n\nYou can move as many cards (which are in a correct sequence) at once on the tableau, as
        there are free stacks available. This corresponds to the rule, that only one card can be moved at once,
        but when there are free stacks available, the cards can be moved on the free stacks first and then
        to the destination stack.
       </string>
    <string name="manual_GrandfathersClock_scoring">From tableau to foundation: +50</string>

    <!-- Vegas -->
    <string name="manual_Vegas_structure">@string/manual_Klondike_structure</string>
    <string name="manual_Vegas_objective">Play cards to the foundation to win more money.</string>
    <string name="manual_Vegas_rules">The rules are identical to the \"Klondike\"-Rules.
        \n\nCards can be placed on the tableau in descending order and
        in alternating colors. You can move a whole sequence of cards at once. On the foundation, cards
        can be placed only in ascending order on the corresponding family.\n\nOnly kings can be placed
        on empty tableau stacks and only aces can be placed on empty foundation stacks.\n\nBy pressing
        on the main stack, cards will be moved to the discard stack from where you can use them.
        The amount of cards depends on the chosen settings. If \"Draw 1\" has been selected, only one card
        will be moved. With \"Draw 3\" enabled, 3 cards will be moved at once.\n\nIf the main stack is empty,
        you can still press on it to move every card from the discard stack to the main stack and use them again.</string>
    <string name="manual_Vegas_scoring">The amount of money you win depends on the bet you set up in the settings.
        You pay eg. 50$ at the beginning of the game, and with every card played to the foundation you win 1/10 of the bet.
        \n\nA game will be saved as won, when the score is above 0. Playing cards back from the foundation costs 2/10 of the bet.
        \n\nUsing the hint or undo functions will also cost 1/10 of the bet.
        \n\nDISCLAIMER: You do not play for real money in this game :)</string>

    <!-- Calculation -->
    <string name="manual_Calculation_structure">1 deck of 52 cards.\n\n4 tableau stacks, 4 foundation
        stacks, 1 main and 1 discard stack</string>
    <string name="manual_Calculation_objective">Place every card to the foundation, regardless of suit, until each foundation
        stack shows a king. The stacks have to be build in the following order:
        \n\n 1. stack in 1s: A, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, J, Q, K     <!-- 1s means: add in each step 1 to the value-->
          \n 2. stack in 2s: 2, 4, 6, 8, 10, Q, A, 3, 5, 7, 9, J, K     <!-- 2s means: add in each step 2 to the value-->
          \n 3. stack in 3s: 3, 6, 9, Q, 2, 5, 8, J, A, 4, 7, 10, K     <!-- ... -->
          \n 4. stack in 4s: 4, 8, Q, 3, 7, J, 2, 6, 10, A, 5, 9, K
        \n\nThe next playable cards are shown above the foundation stacks, too.
    </string>
    <string name="manual_Calculation_rules">The 4 foundation stacks already start with the first cards, which are
        randomly chosen. Cards on the foundation have to follow the order given under Objective.
        \n\nCards from the discard stack can be moved to any tableau stack or on foundation stacks, if they
        fulfill the correct order.

        \n\nPressing the main stack will simply move the card on the discard stack to the tableau stack with the
        fewest cards. Alternative rule: The cards on the discard stack remain there, when pressing on the main stack
        (can be enabled in the game settings).

        \n\nOn the tableau, only top cards can be moved and they can only be moved to the foundation.
       </string>
    <string name="manual_Calculation_scoring">Move a card to foundation: +50</string>


</resources>
